beautyhealthcom.com 2019-01-12

# Privacy Policy - Beauty Health

Privacy of our visitors to beautyhealthcom.com (currently known as beautyhealthcom.com) is very important to us. In my blog, we recognize that the privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information about what types of personal information we obtain and collect when you use and visit the blog, and how we relentlessly guard your information.

We never sell your personal information to others. We use third-party advertising on my blog to support the site. Some of these advertisers may use technologies such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on the site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information that includes their IP address, our viewers ISP, the browser they used to visit our site, and in some cases, if you have Flash installed or not?

Generally, this is used for geographic targeting purposes (showing real estate ads from New York to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads that are based on specific visited sites (such as showing kitchen ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

  1. Google, as an external provider, uses cookies to post ads on its site.
  2. Google's use of the DART cookie allows both he and his partners to post ads to their users based on their visit to their sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  3. Users may choose not to use the DART cookie by visiting the privacy policy of the Google content and ads network.
  4. You can also use this browser plug-in provided by Google to prevent Google Analytics (Google's web analytics software) from tracking it.

I am also using WordPress as a CMS and some add-ons. It may be possible for some add-ons to insert cookies into your computer. As far as I know, I do not know of any add-on that inserts cookies. But if it happens, it is only unconscious and involuntary.

We also use the "Google Display advertising features" for which Google uses Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers. This will not harm the computer (PC, tablet, smartphone, mobile, etc.) at all, as this is an official Google cookie and will only help us obtain some statistics about your demographics.

I use the following feature in the Google Analytics advertising features.

  * Demographics and interest in Google Analytics

The above function is only useful for me and for the only purpose of knowing the statistics of our visitors to provide better content. Sometimes, in the future, based on this data, we can also provide affiliate products that are useful for customers.

You can search Google or use the exclusion options mentioned above to ignore these cookies.
